### **Personal Information**

D.O.B: 25-Jan-1995

Nationality : Ghanaian

Marital status : Single

Languages Spoken: English, Hausa, Twi.

#### Skills

Graphics Design

WordPress

Microsoft Suit

Website Design & Development

UX/UI design (Adobe XD)

Computer Troubleshooting & Repair

Soil, Asphalt and concrete testing.

Typing

# **Education and Training**

**UDEMY** 

**PRESENT** 

**FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT** 

**UDEMY** 

2021

PHP & MYSQL PROGRAMMING / **ETHICAL HACKING & CYBER SECURITY** 

**GHANA TECH LABS** 

2020

**WEB DEVELOPMENT** 

POWER CITY NETWORK(PCN\_ICT)

2016 - 2018

COMPUTER HARWARE AND NETWORKING

CHINA WATER AND ELECTRICAL

2013 - 2015

**SOIL, ASPHALT & CONCRETE TESTING** 

**DAMONGO SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL** 

2010 - 2013

**GENERAL ARTS** 

# **SALIFU FAISAL**



phaisalsalif@gmail.com



Tema – Adjei kojo.



+233 55 862 8473



Dekin graphix

#### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Organized, humble, hardworking with strong time-management. Excellent in multiple task and working on time, broad industry experience such as graphics design, computer hardware, web development and laboratory works.

Good knowledge in HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, PHP, MYSQL, BOOTSTRAP, MONGODB, NODE JS, ADOBE PHOTOSHOP & ILLUSTRATOR, ADOBE XD.

#### **WORKING EXPERIENCE**

#### **Dekin Graphix** Present

Freelancer – Graphic design, UX/UI design, Web development,

Computer troubleshooting, WordPress.

# China Water and Electrical Company - Ghana 2019 - 2020

Assistant Laboratory Technician - Testing of Soil, Concrete and asphalt material for a road and building construction works.

# China Water and Electrical Company – Ghana 2017-2018

Office boy – Entering, keeping, Sort data and appointments.

#### **VigxGH**

2015 - 2016

IT personnel – Troubleshooting computers, graphics & web designer.

# China Water and Electrical Company – Ghana

2013 - 2015

Assistant Laboratory Technician - Testing of Soil, Concrete and Asphalt material for road and building construction works.

#### REFREE

Mohameed Deen - Vigx - +233 50 634 0137

Mr. Tahir - Materials Engineer - +233 20482 0638

Joshua Kumi - Ghana Tech Labs - +233 24 855 9331